Forgive us in advance for this wild weekend
Girls Trip is a comedy, romance, adventure film directed by Malcolm D. Lee.
Four girlfriends take a trip to New Orleans for an annual festival and, along the way,
rediscover their wild sides and strengthen the bonds of sisterhood.
Ryan Pierce, played by Regina Hall.
Sasha Franklin, played by Queen Latifah.
Lisa Cooper, played by Jada Pinkett Smith.
Dina, played by Tiffany Haddish.
Julian Stevens, played by Larenz Tate.
Stewart Pierce, played by Mike Colter.
Girls Trip is a 2017 American comedy film starring Regina Hall,
Tiffany Haddish, Jada Pinkett Smith and Queen Latifah.
The film is directed by Malcolm D.
Lee and written by Kenya Barris and Tracy Oliver, from a story by the pair and Erica
Rivinoja, who based the script off their own experiences with their female friends.
The film follows a group of four friends who go to New Orleans to attend the
Essence Music Festival in order to reconnect after a long time.
The film premiered in June 2017 and received multiple awards and nominations, most notably at the
49th NAACP Image Awards, with Haddish's performance receiving critical acclaim.
A sequel has long been in development; in March 2025, one of the film's producers announced that
the project had a completed script and that all four stars would be returning.
The film explores themes of concert, female friendship,
hallucinogenic drug, festival, public urination.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.